masseys.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

Our Commitment to Privacy  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

The Information We Collect:  
Masseys® and its parent company Mason® Companies, Inc. value and respect your privacy. We collect information about you through our websites and catalog orders in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate our products, services, and promotions to you.

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Masseys website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive catalogs or mailings. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number  
*Credit/Debit Card Information (This is only when you place an order)

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's name and address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are only the name and address of the other person.

Communication Consent  
You authorized us, our affiliates, agents, and others calling at our request or on our behalf to contact you at any number or email address you have provided to us or have used to contact us or which is lawfully obtained by or on our behalf for the servicing, management and/or collection of your account. We may contact you in any manner consistent with the information we have obtained, including e-mail, telephone calls and text messages. We may use automated technology for the purpose of contacting you, including but not limited to automatic dialing or similar equipment. We may monitor or record calls from you to us and calls from us to you. When you give us your mobile telephone number we may contact you at that number using automated dialing equipment and we can leave pre-recorded or other messages, even if you are charged for it by your provider.

The Way We Use Information:  
We use the information you provide when placing an order to complete that order. From time to time, we may share information we have collected among our other divisions and, under certain circumstances, with third parties that provide services on our behalf or with carefully screened companies whose products or services we feel may interest you. If you do not wish us to share this information, please relay your request along with your mailing address to us by phone toll free at 1-866-229-2316 or write to us at:

Masseys  
1251 1st Avenue  
Chippewa Falls, WI 54729

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out.

Third Party Advertising  
We may contract with third-party companies who use cookies to measure the performance of a marketing effort on our behalf. We may share your personally identifiable information, including your name, address, email address, as well as a record of any transactions you conduct on our website or offline with us with a third-party advertising partner and its service providers in order to deliver to you banner advertisements and other advertising tailored to your interests when you visit certain websites. Our advertising partner will make the data we provide it anonymous.

To learn about opt-out programs that this and other third-party advertising companies participate in as well as the effects of opting out, please visit the following websites: http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/, http://www.aboutads.info/choices/.

Bazaarvoice’s use of any data collected through its cookies is subject to the [Bazaarvoice Privacy Policy](http://go.bazaarvoice.com/FDbGe00Sd0P0M30S000DyEi) and is reflected in our [Service Descriptions](http://go.bazaarvoice.com/kP0ee0E000M03GySbD0Ti0D).

Cookies  
Masseys.com uses cookies (small text files placed on your device) to help enhance your shopping experience on our website. Cookies allow us to personalize and streamline your shopping experience. We realize that some shoppers choose to not allow cookies, so we have created our site to not be dependent on them. If you choose to not allow cookies, you will be able to select a product and complete a purchase on our site, but you will not be able to take advantage of some of our advanced functionality. Please be aware that your privacy and security are our top concerns - we do not store any personally identifiable or sensitive information in the cookie.

If you would like more information about cookies and how to manage them, please see the following websites: http://www.microsoft.com/info/cookies.mspx, http://computer.howstuffworks.com/cookie.htm

Analytics  
Masseys.com collects and analyzes certain information about its customers and their browsing and purchasing patterns. To learn more about Google Analytics’ privacy practices and the opt-out choices it offers, please visit the following websites: https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245, https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/.

Our Commitment to Data Security features Secure Site Class 3 Authentication by VeriSign®  
Masseys uses VeriSign, which offers state-of-the-art, completely dependable security infrastructure and is the most trusted, recognized, security brand on the web. Secure Site by VeriSign provides the ultimate in credibility for online transactions. You can be confident each purchase is backed by the most reliable, secure operations infrastructure, comprehensive security, trust, and authentication practices. VeriSign authentication procedures have withstood the most rigorous scrutiny from independent third-party auditors. In fact, VeriSign is the only Certificate Authority in the world to have passed an extensive independent Type #SAS 70 audit by KPMG, the global accounting and consulting firm. (The Statement of Auditing Standard 70, Type #SAS 70, was established by the American Institute of Certified Public Accountants to certify trusted practices.) For more information visit [VeriSign](http://www.verisign.com/).

Masseys has taken several steps to ensure Your Credit Card Transactions are Secure GUARANTEED. Our servers use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) advanced encryption. Masseys uses state-of-the-art technology to protect your personal information and privacy. All credit card transactions are secured by 128-bit encryption. As an added measure, in the unlikely event of a credit card fraud, there is still no risk to you. The Fair Credit Act states that your credit card company can hold you liable for a maximum of $50.00 in fraudulent charges. Masseys.com will reimburse for any charges up to the $50.00 maximum your credit card company can charge you if those charges result from an order you placed on our secure server. You can enjoy shopping worry free at Masseys.

How We Use Your Email Address  
When you provide us your email address, we will email you as necessary to process your order, respond to a request, or to provide customer service. After you place an order at Masseys.com, you will receive an email confirmation. If you receive one of our Masseys gift cards will also receive an email notifying you of the gift and instructions on how to use the card.  
Masseys may also send promotional emails about products, offers, or services that we think you may be interested in. Masseys will only send promotional emails to people who wish to receive them. Instructions on how to unsubscribe can be found in each of our email mailings.

Masseys and our parent company Mason® Companies, Inc. value and respect your privacy. We collect information about you through our websites and when you place an order with us in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about our products, services, and promotions. As described in this policy, from time to time, we may share your information among our other titles and, under certain circumstances, with third parties that provide services on our behalf or with whom we have partnered to offer a particular product or service.

Our Commitment to Children's Privacy  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. Therefore, we comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), do not permit registration by, and will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. No part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13 years of age.

How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information  
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting us either by phone at 1-866-229-2316 or writing to us at:

Masseys  
1251 1st Avenue  
Chippewa Falls, WI 54729

We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

Changes To This Privacy Policy Statement  
From time to time, we may use the information you provide to us for in ways not mentioned above in this Privacy Notice. If our policies change at some point of time, we will post the changes on the Privacy Notice page of our website. From time to time, you should check this page for more information on how we use the data we collect.

How To Contact Us  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these security and privacy policies, please call us at 1-866-229-2316 or send us an email at service@masseys.com

OTHER LEGAL INFORMATION

Product Information  
The products displayed at this Site are available while supplies last. The prices displayed at this Site are quoted in U.S. dollars.

Links To Other Web Sites And Services  
This Site may contain links to outside services or resources that Masseys does not control. Any concern about these services and resources should be directed to that outside Site. First, try to work this out with the Linked Site. If you are not able to resolve it, please let us know.

Terms Of Use  
We welcome you to the Masseys website. The rules that apply to your use of our Site are set forth in on this webpage. By using our Site you are agreeing to those rules. We reserve the right to change the rules from time to time. Your ongoing use of the Site means that you agree to the rules as changed.

Property Rights  
The entire Site as a whole is protected by copyright and trade dress laws. All rights, ownership and interest in are owned by Masseys and its parent companies. All identified trademarks appearing at the site are trademarks of Masseys and its parent companies and all affiliated trademarks of other companies are used with permission. One or more patents may apply to this web site, including without limitations: US Patent Nos. 5,528,490; 5,761,649; 7,908,173; and 7,908,176. Excepting trademarks and brand names of third parties for merchandise depicted on the Site, or as otherwise noted, all images, materials, designs, photographs, illustrations, icons, videos and other materials that are part of this Site are copyrights, trademarks, trade dress and/or other intellectual properties owned, controlled or licensed by Masseys and its parent companies. Our Site as a whole, and its contents, are intended solely for personal, non-commercial use by Site users. It is permissible to download or copy contents and other materials subject to downloaded capability displayed on the Site for personal use only. No right, title or interest in any downloaded images or materials or software is transferred to you as a result of any personal copying or downloading. As a Site user, you may not reproduce (except for personal use as noted above), publish, transmit, distribute, display, modify, create derivative works from, sell or participate in any sale of, or otherwise utilize in any way, in whole or in part, any of the Contents, the Site, or any related software without the express written permission of Masseys.

Identity Theft Prevention Program, known as our Red Flag Policy  
The risk to our customers, employees and business partners from data loss and identity theft is of significant concern. All of our employees and business partners share in the responsibility of reducing this risk and protecting applicable information for which they have access or custodianship.

The purpose of the program is to establish an designed to detect, prevent and mitigate identity theft in connection with the opening of a covered account or an existing covered account and to provide for continued administration of the Program in compliance with Part 681 of Title 16 of the Code of Federal Regulations implementing Sections 114 and 315 of the Fair and Accurate Credit Transactions Act (FACTA) of 2003. For further information on "Red Flag" requirements go to http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/edu/microsites/redflagsrule/faqs.shtm
